Do you ever wish Hamas had not committed October 7th?
Aside from the fact that Christiana Amanpour is far too tenured and experienced of a journalist
to ask Uncle YL this nonsensical and insensitive and quite honestly unintellectual of a question,
I want to point out what someone said in the comments, which was, well, she may have been forced to.
This passive U.S. society has now turned grace into enabling of spinelessness.
As someone in media, I want you to understand something.
No one is forced to do anything because the biggest threat is you'll lose your job.
Forced to do something is when you're told, if you don't do this, we will merc your family.
Forced to do something is, if you don't do this, we'll cut off the other finger.
Forced to do something is when actual force is presented upon you.
Being told you have to do this or you'll lose your job is not force.
And anybody in media who you see continuing to show up this way or who you've seen show up this way,
I want you to know they made a choice.
They weren't forced.
They made a choice.
They chose to ignore speaking about Gassa.
They've chosen to continue speaking about Donald Trump favorably.
They chose to not question Kamala Harris or Joe Biden and their very problematic lack of policy and genocidal policies.
Those were choices.
And they decided, I will not go against this because either I don't want to lose my job because I feel I'm the only voice that can speak.
Or I don't want to lose my job because I have to take care of my family, etc.
Whatever.
And I know there's people that are like, I respect that.
I don't.
Because these people are getting paid monies.
Okay?
So this concept of they were forced to when it is referring to people in the entertainment space, we got to cut that out.
They chose to.
And they played themselves.
And that goes for you too, Gail, and that other brother who'll be sitting up there next to you looking a mess.